=Ex-Wife Stop S2=
= توقف الزوجة السابقة S2 =
=Episode 12=
= الحلقة 12 =
If it hadn't been for your inability,
إذا لم يكن ذلك بسبب عدم قدرتك ،
Sheng Nanfang would have died.
سيموت شنغ نانفانغ.
It's getting tricky now.
أصبح الأمر معقدًا الآن.
They have made up with each other
لقد تصالحوا مع بعضهم البعض
and they are ganging up on me.
وهم يتحدون علي.
Don't let
لا تدع
that mistake happen again.
هذا الخطأ يحدث مرة أخرى.
What's wrong, Mom?
ما بك يا أمي؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
I'll get someone to clean it up.
سأجعل شخصًا ينظفها.
No need.
لا حاجة.
You will be at the helm of the Tianqi Group.
ستكون على رأس مجموعة Tianqi Group.
Take the long view
خذ نظرة طويلة
and don't care about such small things.
ولا تهتم بمثل هذه الأشياء الصغيرة.
There is an important task for you now.
هناك مهمة مهمة بالنسبة لك الآن.
(Do you want to know)
(هل تريد أن تعرف)
(who's behind the Hechuan project?)
(من يقف وراء مشروع Hechuan؟)
Who are you?
من أنت؟
(I'll be waiting for you in the underground parking lot.)
(سأنتظرك في موقف السيارات تحت الأرض.)
Mr. Sheng, I've heard a lot about you.
السيد شنغ ، لقد سمعت الكثير عنك.
I'm Su Tinghao.
أنا سو تينغاو.
Vice President of the Tianqi Group.
نائب رئيس مجموعة Tianqi.
I've heard of you.
لقد سمعت عنك.
Make your point quickly.
اشرح وجهة نظرك بسرعة.
I'm really curious
أنا فضولي حقًا
about what it's like living with a woman
حول ما يشبه العيش مع امرأة
who's scheming to wreck your company
من الذي يخطط لتدمير شركتك
every day.
كل يوم.
You only have five minutes.
لديك خمس دقائق فقط.
Okay.
تمام.
There's another intention behind her cooperation with your group.
هناك نية أخرى وراء تعاونها مع مجموعتك.
She has already agreed to the proposal of acquiring the Sheng's Group,
لقد وافقت بالفعل على اقتراح الحصول على مجموعة Sheng ،
and she's just waiting for the stock price
وهي فقط تنتظر سعر السهم
to hit a new low.
للوصول إلى مستوى منخفض جديد.
All the executives at the Tianqi Group know about this plan.
يعرف جميع المديرين التنفيذيين في مجموعة Tianqi هذه الخطة.
Only you
أنت فقط
don't know it.
لا تعرف ذلك.
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
She promised me a sum of money,
وعدتني بمبلغ من المال ،
and it'll come into our account in a few days.
وسيظهر في حسابنا في غضون أيام قليلة.
I can assure you
يمكنني أن أؤكد لكم
that she can't afford the money,
أنها لا تستطيع تحمل المال ،
and the project you're working on together
والمشروع الذي تعملون عليه معًا
will be affected.
سيتأثر.
Mr. Sheng.
السيد شنغ.
We're on the same side.
نحن في نفس الجانب.
This is to show my sincerity.
هذا لإظهار إخلاصي.
It contains the evidence of Su Shaoyan's covert interference
يحتوي على دليل على تدخل Su Shaoyan السري
with the Hechuan project.
مع مشروع Hechuan.
And there is an acquisition contract with her signature.
وهناك عقد استحواذ بتوقيعها.
I've already sent it to you.
لقد أرسلته لك بالفعل.
Mr. Sheng, take a good look at it.
السيد شنغ ، ألق نظرة فاحصة عليه.
(Do you really think she loves you?)
(هل تعتقد حقًا أنها تحبك؟)
(She's already hooked up with her childhood sweetheart.)
(لقد ارتبطت بالفعل بحبيبة طفولتها).
(Once you cease to be useful,)
(بمجرد أن تتوقف عن أن تكون مفيدًا ،)
(she will dump you.)
(سوف تتخلص منك.)
(Acquisition Contract)
(عقد الاستحواذ)
Mr. Sheng.
السيد شنغ.
Here's the cell phone that was broken on the day of your accident.
هذا هو الهاتف الخلوي الذي تعرض للكسر في يوم الحادث.
It has been fixed,
تم اصلاحه،
and the data in it has been restored.
وتمت استعادة البيانات الموجودة فيه.
(Acquisition Contract)
(عقد الاستحواذ)
(Su Shaoyan)
(سو شاويان)
It's true that someone in the company suggested acquiring the Sheng's Group,
صحيح أن أحدًا في الشركة اقترح الاستحواذ على مجموعة Sheng ،
but I refused.
لكني رفضت.
You've put tremendous effort into the Sheng's Group.
لقد بذلت جهدًا هائلاً في مجموعة Sheng.
How can I do anything to hurt you?
كيف يمكنني فعل أي شيء يؤذيك؟
(She has been lying to me,)
(لقد كانت تكذب علي)
(both before)
(كلاهما من قبل)
(and after I lost my memory.)
(وبعد أن فقدت ذاكرتي).
(I can't believe I was stupid enough to believe her.)
(لا أصدق أنني كنت غبيًا بما يكفي لتصديقها).